Oooh, ugh.
Come on, Mr. Blue Guy!
You've gotta wake up!
Wake up!
It hurts.  Just let me die.
You can't die, I'm bored!
All these girls want to talk about is chick stuff,
and not the fun chick stuff,
like ribbons and unicorns.
I don't have treads,
but I often find them staring at things
they really shouldn't be.
You see??  Boring stuff, like oppression, and a hostile work environment.
Get Doc.  I need Doc.
I can't!  He got possessed by the evil guy and they escaped!
He is the one who shot you, don't you remember?
I know, I want him to shoot me again.
Now now now.  Sounds like someone has a case of the poor me's.
If you were going to die, you would have done it by now.
Maybe, you just need to realize you're
going to have to live with intense pain.
Get that Sarge guy.  Have him make me a new body.
Oh, we can't.  We're out of parts because we overused that joke!
And Sarge has left with the others to chase Doc!
Don't worry, they left a long time ago, so I'm sure they'll be back any minute.
Simmons had a fool-proof plan to catch them.
Hello...hello?  Is anybody here?
Just great.  I guess we all got separated in the teleporter.
Sarge!  This is Simmons 2.0, do you read me?
Apparently your plan to chase Lopez and Doc has failed miserably.
I appear to be stuck in some sort of nexus of teleporters which could take me anywhere in the universe.
Or...it's a janitor's close.  Hell, I don't fucking know.
Sarge, are you there, Sarge!?
Hello!  Anyone!  Do you read me?
Do I read you?  Anyone?  Anybody?  Nobody?  Okay.
Well, I don't think the others are coming.  We must have gotten separated somehow.
My toes...are getting pruny.
Oookay.  Why don't we try to find O'Malley?
I know where you can find O'Malley.  He lived inside my helmet for a while.
Maybe he left his address to send his mail.  We were like friends.
Sounds like he took some of the furniture when he left.
And the carpet.  And the drapes.  And I wouldn't expect to get that deposit back, if you know what I mean.
Sergeant!  Look!  A sleeping person!
What?  Holy macaroni!
He's not sleeping son, he's dead.
Oh good.  At first, I thought that was me,
because I am blue, and I like to sleep.
But, if he is dead, that can not be me.  That would be silly.
No doubt he was called by our very enemy.  Once again I find myself torn.
On the one hand, there's one less Blue in the universe.
But now Doc's got a bigger body count than me!  That just won't do!
So screw it.
Rest in peace, scumbag.
Look!  More sleeping people!  It must be nap time!
But who has nap time now?  Nap time comes before ?pant? time, not after.
I think these people are just making up times.
What the Samuel Hell stinky happened here?
It must have been an enormous battle.
Hello!  Is anyone okay?
Are there any survivors?
Preferably any red survivors?
Don't let that discourage you from speaking up if you're blue, I won't step on your neck or anything like that.
Am I allowed to answer?
Sshhh.  Quiet.  Do you here that?
Yes.  That noise is called water.
It is very wet, and very sloshy--
I was talking about the trumpet, bluetard.
I have to go to the bathroom now for some reason.
Which is odd, because I already went when we were standing in the creek together.
Wait a minute, I know that song, that's Reveille!
Why would someone be playing Reveille in the middle of the--
Yaaaah!!
Sweet gibbly giblets!
Running time!
What just happened here?
I think all the sleeping people were trying to--
That was rhetorical!
Get over here, give me a boost!
Okay!  You are a nice person and people say good things about you.
Not a morale boost, moron, a physical one!
I need to see what's in that window!
That window is very high.  I don't think you are tall enough.
I know, I need you to help me look through it.
I don't think I am tall enough either.  Also, my head is round.  That window is square.
Come here, you.
Whoa!
What do you see?
I see....a room.
And?? What's in the room?
There are some walls, and some ceilings...wait, just one ceiling.
What's making all that racket?
(chanting) Kill the Reds!  Kill the Reds!
You are not going to like it.
Caboose, I have a very bad feeling about this.
What's that?
Chaaaarge!!
Come on Caboose, we gotta get to the higher ground.
Come on, Caboose!
Sarge, I am scared of our new friends.
Hot 'n sunny bono, what's going on here?
Stop fighting, stop fighting, everyone stop fighting!
Everyone, look unto me, I possess the blue flag!
It's more beautiful than I ever imagined!
I have seen the top of the mountain, and you will worship me as though I were a god!
I regret nothing!  I lived as few men dare to dream!
Oh you fucking camping bitch!
It's a legitimate strategy!
Whoa!
Damn!
Hey Blue, we're the only two left!  Let's work together!
What do you mean?
I'm coming out!
Okay! I'm coming out too!
What did you mean, we could work as a team?
I bash you in the head with my rifle, and you die.
Good teamwork, you fucking noob!
Good game, good game everybody, gg man gg!
I have no earthly idea what it is I just saw or what this place is or where in the hell O'Malley is!
My only choice is to blame Griff for coming up with such a flawed plan.  Stupid, stupid Griff.
I am so confused.  Where is Church?  I need Church to tell me what to think.
Church can handle this.  He can handle anything!
Hey asshole, for the last time, let me out of this damn jail cell!
Yeah, let him out, he's driving me nuts!
Aw, shut up Red, nobody asked you!
I should have never listened to Donut's stupid fucking plan.