Hey.
Yeah?
You ever wonder why we're here?
That's one of life's great mysteries, isn't it?
Why are we here?
I mean, are we the product of some cosmic coincidence,
or is there really a God, watching everything...
with a plan for us and stuff?
I don't know, man, but it keeps me up at night.
What?
I mean, why are we out here, in this canyon
Oh, uhhhh, I....
Yeah
What was all that stuff about God?
Uhhh....hm?  Nothing.
You wanna talk about it?
No.
You sure?
Yeah.
Seriously, though, why are we out here?
As far as I can tell,
it's just a box canyon in the middle of nowhere.
no way in or out,
the only reason that we set up a red base over here
is because they have a blue base over there.
and the only reason they have a blue base over there
is because we have a red base over here.
Yeah, that's cause we're fighting each other.
No, but, I mean,
even if we were to pull out today,
and they were to come take our base,
they would have two bases in the middle of a box canyon,
Whoop-de-fuckin' doo.
What's up with that, anyway?
I mean, I signed on to fight some aliens.
Next thing I know, Masterchief
blows up the whole Covenant armada
and I'm stuck in the middle of nowhere
fightin' a bunch of blue guys.
What are they doing?
What??
I said, what are they doing now?
God damn, I'm getting so sick
of answering that question.
Hey, you have the fuckin' rifle,
I can't see shit, don't bitch
at me because
I'm not gonna just sit up here
and play with my dick all day.
Okay, look, they're just standing there,
and talking, okay?
That's all they're doing,
that's all they ever do,
is just stand there and talk.
That's what they were doing last week,
that's what they were doing
when you asked me five minutes ago.
So five minutes from now,
when you ask me, "what are they doin'?",
my answer's gonna be,
they're still just talkin',
and they're still just standin' there.
What are they talking about?
You know what?
I fuckin' hate you.
Talk about a waste of resources,
I mean, we should be out there,
finding new and intelligent forms of life,
you know, fight them.
Yeah, no shit.
That's why they should put us in charge.
Ladies!
Front and center on the double!
(Fuck.) Yes, sir!