Hi everyone, I'm private Dick Simmons.
And I'm private Church.
We're here today to talk to you about the soaring cost of energy prices.
Specifically, gasoline.
Gas prices are so high right now
that some people are having to cut back on basic necessities
just to afford to drive to work.
Not me, I just quit goin' to work.
To help understand the seemingly never-ending rising gas prices,
I asked my good friend Church
to build us a primer to explain
the complex economic system behind gasoline production and distribution.
Yeah, that actually turned out to be a lot more reading than I thought,
so I just rented a copy of Mad Max instead.
From what I can tell, the gas crisis has something to do with people in Australia
that really like effiminate bondage.
You knuckleheads have got it COMPLETELY wrong as usual.
High gas prices aren't caused by supply and demand!
It's all the taxes!
Taxes?
That's right! Don't you know for every dollar you spend on regular unleaded gasoline,
the government takes 137 cents!
Sir, I think that your math might be a liiiitle off.
And they tax you more for the good stuff!
That's why mid-grade and premium are exactly 10 cents more per gallon!
no matter how much regular costs.
That doesn't make any sense...or wait, does it?
Besides, everyone knows that gasoline comes from dinosaurs!
If we're running out of gas, the solution isn't to drive less,
it's to kill more dinosaurs!
All the dinosaurs are already dead.
It doesn't have to be just dinosaurs, moron!
Any animal turns into oil when it dies.
So remember, if you want to be environmentally friendly,
just kill every living thing you see, and bury it.
But that process takes millions of years!
I've got time.
Let me out of here!  There's worms!
Gentlemen, we could debate the fine points all day.
But the fact remains,
a gallon of gas still costs less today
than a gallon of milk.
Yeah, but you don't drink three gallons of milk every time you drive to work.
Maybe you don't.
Well, we may never figure out why gas costs so much,
but you can at least take steps to save money.
First, try cutting out other petroleum-based products besides gasoline,
like paraffin wax, loop oil, synthetic latex, and rubber.
Man, Doughnut just saved a ton of money right there.
Of course, the easiest way to save is on your commute.
Like try switching your current daily driver to a smaller vehicle,
instead of the full-size you probably drive now.
Or you could try carpooling to work.
or how 'bout this, how 'bout you use your own two feet and walk?
Ah, don't be a pussy.
Of course, cutting back on the amount of gas you use can be difficult.
Most people have a near insatiable thirst for gas.
(sarcastically) I know I do!
Me too!  I drank two gallons this morning!
Caboose!  I wasn't using the word 'thirst' literally!
No...my tummy feels a little weird.
Blaaappp!
You know, that could actually be a lot of fun at parties.
Ugh, I'm just glad it came out his mouth.
Hey Simmons, give me a ride back to base!
Yes, sir!
Doh, great.  Has anybody got a gallon of unleaded?
How about a jug of milk?